

UX & VR DESIGNER









CA, USA

anhnguyen19903@gmail.com

(714) 483 4589

http://dawnuxi.com

Design to empower people, solve human problems and create delightful human-centric experience Passionate in AR/VR, Artificial Intelligence and Data Visualization technology

Experienced designing and developing website, mobile app, VR app and data visualization software Set a goal to design a collaborative innovative environment where everyone can come together and innovate.

| Skills | Tools |
|--------|-------|
|--------|-------|

| Sketching | Branding | Design Thinking | Photoshop | Proto.io |
|--------------------------|--------------------------|-----------------|-----------------|---------------|
| HTML5/CSS3 | Content Strategy | 3D Modeling | After Effects | Mapbox Studio |
| JQuery | Agile Development | 3D Rendering | Illustrators | Framer |
| Prototyping | Interaction Design | Animation | Premiere | Origami |
| Usability Testing | Information Architecture | UI/UX | Sketch3 | Principle |
| A/B testing | Video Editing | VR/AR | Paper & Markers | Unity3D |
| Wireframing | Critical Thinking | Swift | Dreamweaver | Invision |
| Analytics | User Research | Java | Animate/Flash | Houdini |
| Personas | Motion Graphics | C# | Edge Animate | Solidworks |

Experience

8/2018-Present Lead UX & Data Viz Designer - Corelogic Innovation Lab Santa Monica, CA Leading Discovery and Framing Process for Business Intelligence product development Exploring and building future innovative visions for Big Data Visualization

Leading UX Design for Geospatial Visualization project

Leading and managing VR Experience projects and keeping Corelogic on the cutting edge of leverage technology to drive business outcomes

5/2018-Present Co-Founder, Chief Designer & Visionary - Virtision.com
Leading and building UX language and Agile practices for VR experience development
Designing vision and finding innovative opportunity for Virtision's growth
Working closely with designers and engineers from end-to-end product development

8/2017-5/2018 UI/UX & VR Design Engineer - Syngenta US champaign, IL Designed and built the lab become an interactive environment for innovation Designed and developed interactive interface and motion graphics for websites Delivered high quality digital products on a timely manner Conducted user experience research and designing web and mobile application

Participated brainstorming, ideation and project development stage.

5/2017-5/2018 UI/UX & VR Intern - National Center for Supercomputing Application Champaign, IL Designed user interface and produced high-quality prototypes for data visualization software collaboration with NASA.

Designed Virtual Reality Controller and interfaces for AVL's Virtual Director software in order to improve Scientific Data Visualization Design's experience, workflows and collaboration with scientists

Produced a demo of AVL's works to show in SIGGRAPH 2017 and got featured on Discovery Channel Designed and developed Virtual Reality experience on WebVR platform to showcase dome view production

Conducted User Experience Research and delivered excellent design strategies Led and redesigned Advanced Visualization Lab's web interface to attract and engage the general public to computational scientific research and contents better

Produced low and medium quality prototypes to test and learning user behavior

2016-8/2017 Video Producer & Motion Designer – University of Illinois Housing Champaign, IL Filmed and edited commercial and event videos as well as design and animated motion graphics for advertisement and marketing's projects

2011–2013 Front-End Web Developer - Maarka Data Solutions Irvine, CA Designed and developed better UX/UI on the company's old website

Education

😭 University of Illinois, at Urbana-Champaign

Industrial Design - Class of 2018 with Honors
Industrial Design Society of America | Member
Siebel Design Center VR Project | UI and VR designer
CUBE Consulting | Design Consultant & Web Developer

Awards

UIUC's Student Employee of the Year 2017-2018